hi folks so welcome back and now we'll
大家好，欢迎回来，现在我们将
be talking a bit about mechanism design
谈论机制设计
in general so the idea here is that in a
一般来说，这里的想法是
lot of what we've looked at so far in
到目前为止，我们已经看过很多
the course we've been looking at
我们一直在看的课程
specific institution specific games and
特定机构特定的游戏和
trying to understand how they affect
试图了解它们如何影响
behavior and in particular how the
行为，尤其是
structure of the game can be used to
游戏的结构可以用来
analyze and predict how people going to
分析和预测人们如何去
behave and now what we want to do is
表现，现在我们要做的是
flip things upside down so this will be
颠倒东西，这将是
game theory on its head and the idea is
博弈论从头到尾都是
instead of taking the game is given and
而不是采取游戏，
trying to analyze it we'll look at
试图分析它，我们将看
situations where we have some idea of
我们有一些想法的情况
what we'd like to see be the outcome and
我们希望看到的是结果，
then the question is can we design a
那么问题是我们可以设计一个
game that will yield that outcome so can
会产生这种结果的游戏
we design institutions and you know one
我们设计机构，您知道一个
big puzzle that we have in terms of the
就我们而言，这是一个大难题
way people behave is when you think
人们的行为方式就是当您认为
about the inefficiency that goes on in
关于持续的低效率
terms of bargaining there's often
讨价还价的条件经常是
bargaining breakdowns and people spend a
讨价还价的故障，人们花了
lot of time trying to figure out how do
很多时间试图弄清楚怎么做
we mediate bargaining what's an
我们调解讨价还价
appropriate technique to bring two sides
带两个方面的适当技巧
together so that they can reach a
在一起，以便他们可以达到
bargain and in terms of complete
讨价还价和完整
information game theory if people can
信息博弈论
really see what the payoffs are and you
真的看到了回报，你
looked at a particular bargaining game
看过一个讨价还价的游戏
generally you would have situations
通常情况下
where people would tend to reach
人们倾向于到达的地方
agreements they can look down the tree
他们可以看不起树的协议
they can figure out what's going to
他们可以弄清楚会发生什么
happen and and unravel things and reach
发生并解散事物并达到
an agreement and so here we can ask a
协议，所以在这里我们可以问一个
question of well let's suppose now that
好问题，让我们现在假设
we're in a Bayesian setting so we have a
我们处于贝叶斯环境，所以我们有一个
situation where we have workers thinking
我们有工人思考的情况
about trying to get higher wages and we
关于试图获得更高的工资，我们
have management and shareholders on the
拥有管理层和股东
other side trying to keep wages low and
另一方试图保持低工资，
each wants different things coming out
每个人都想要不同的东西出来
of a new agreement a labor agreement can
新协议中的劳动协议可以
we design a way in which they're going
我们设计他们前进的方式
to come to a table and make offers and
来一张桌子并提出要约
counteroffers in such a way that they'd
还价的方式是
actually reach an agreement and avoid a
实际上达成协议，避免
strike and avoid wasting resources and
罢工，避免浪费资源，
and time we see strikes all the time so
和时间，我们一直看到罢工，所以
the answer evidently seems to be no we
答案显然是不，我们
can't necessarily design such a
不一定设计这样的
procedure so the question becomes what
程序，所以问题变成什么
procedures can we design what are the
我们可以设计什么程序
best that we can do
尽我们所能
how do we begin to think about that how
我们如何开始思考
do we begin to model designing an
我们开始进行模型设计吗
institution and then seeing what the
机构，然后看看
outcomes are going to be and trying to
结果将是并试图
design the best institution in terms of
设计最佳机构
those outcomes so we'll be looking at
这些结果，所以我们将研究
things like auction design we'll talk
拍卖设计之类的东西
about why we might have breakdown and
关于为什么我们可能会崩溃，
inefficiency in bargaining settings when
谈判时效率低下
people have private information about
人们有关于的私人信息
what they'd like to see be the outcome
他们希望看到的结果
we're going to look at we've already had
我们要看看我们已经有
a look at voting rules but we'll look at
看看投票规则，我们来看看
a general set of decision mechanisms
一套通用的决策机制
that public enterprises can use to
公营企业可以用来
improve efficiency so we're going to
提高效率，所以我们要
look at in some specific detail at how
详细了解如何
to design things when we want to achieve
在我们想要实现时设计事物
efficiency we want to get the best
我们想要获得最好的效率
possible outcomes and we realize that
可能的结果，我们意识到
people have private information and
人们拥有私人信息，
they're going to try and take advantage
他们将尝试并利用
of that and have incentives to try and
并有动机去尝试
get the best that they can get out which
得到最好的，他们可以摆脱
doesn't necessarily always coincide with
不一定总是与
social efficiency so when is it that we
社会效率，那么我们什么时候
can get socially efficient outcomes
可以获得社会有效的结果
that's going to be the central question
这将是核心问题
in mechanism design so let's get started
在机制设计上，让我们开始吧